<Audiobook Narration>

    <ASSIGN_VOICE>
    STORYTELLER=This_is_the_voice_of_a_Knight_in_shining_armor_with_a_noble_voice_high_quality_professional_recording_high_quality_voice_acting;
    JOHN=This_is_a_soft_melodic_bright_timbre_voice_with_a_high_pitched_pitch_belonging_to_a_young_adult_masculine_man;
    JENNIFFER=This_is_a_soft_melodic_bright_timbre_voice_with_a_low_pitched_pitch_belonging_to_a_young_adult_feminine_woman;
    NICOLE=This_is_a_harsh_rough_dark_timbre_voice_with_a_high_pitched_pitch_belonging_to_a_young_adult_feminine_woman;
    BARBARA=This_is_a_soft_melodic_bright_timbre_voice_with_a_medium_pitched_pitch_belonging_to_a_elderly_feminine_woman;
    HENRY=This_is_a_soft_melodic_dark_timbre_voice_with_a_high_pitched_pitch_belonging_to_a_elderly_masculine_man;
    </ASSIGN_VOICE>

    <IMAGE 1>
    A sweeping aerial view of Bennington at dawn! Narrow roads wind among tall trees, and classic wooden homes show peeling paint and simple porches. Gentle early light reveals a quiet town, giving an impression of serenity with an undercurrent of hidden secrets! High-quality visual novel style. HQ WELLSHAPED ANIME
    </IMAGE 1>

    <STORYTELLER>
    <Interest>
    The morning sun glides over the rooftops of Bennington, unveiling a patchwork of old fences, winding lanes, and whispered curiosities lurking beneath everyday life.
    </Interest>
    <Contemplation>
    In one modest house on the outskirts, a spark of youthful ambition meets an undercurrent of anxiety. This is the home of John and his older sister Jennifer, both on the cusp of defining their futures.
    </Contemplation>
    </STORYTELLER>

    <IMAGE 2>
    A young man of slender build stands in a modest bedroom. He has short brown hair that often spikes in random directions, wearing a faded t-shirt featuring an adventure movie motif. A worn leather-bound notebook sits on his desk, sketches of ancient maps visible. His posture shows quiet eagerness and slight uncertainty in his eyes. High-quality visual novel style. HQ WELLSHAPED ANIME
    </IMAGE 2>
    <JOHN>
    <Contemplation>
    "I keep daydreaming about hidden tombs and lost temples! But what if I never measure up to those heroes I admire...?"
    </Contemplation>
    </JOHN>

    <STORYTELLER>
    <Reflection>
    John has devoured stories of archaeologists braving ancient depths since childhood. Yet, he quietly wonders if his courage will fail when true challenges arise.
    </Reflection>
    </STORYTELLER>

    <IMAGE 3>
    A young woman, slightly taller than her brother, sits at a cluttered desk. She has chestnut-brown hair pinned back, wearing simple jeans and a sweater. A thick medical textbook lies open before her, and her eyes show a mixture of determination and underlying dread. High-quality visual novel style. HQ WELLSHAPED ANIME
    </IMAGE 3>
    <JENNIFFER>
    <Fear>
    "I must not let them see how afraid I am... If I crack the mystery of aging, maybe I can silence this terror about death forever."
    </Fear>
    </JENNIFFER>

    <STORYTELLER>
    <Thoughtfulness>
    For Jennifer, knowledge is both a sword and a shield. She immerses herself in medical research, pushing beyond ordinary limits to find answers that could grant more time... or so she hopes.
    </Thoughtfulness>
    </STORYTELLER>

    <IMAGE 4>
    A cozy living room. Barbara, an average-built woman with kind brown eyes, stands near a floral sofa, wearing a pastel blouse. Henry, her husband with graying hair, gazes out the window, a curious spark in his expression. The mood suggests quiet family bonds and subtle worries. High-quality visual novel style. HQ WELLSHAPED ANIME
    </IMAGE 4>
    <STORYTELLER>
    <Warmth>
    Before leaving for their 25th anniversary getaway at a nearby wellness retreat, Barbara and Henry felt reassured, hoping the short trip would refresh their spirits.
    </Warmth>
    <SubtleUnease>
    Yet, a glimmer of concern lingered beneath their smiles, an intuition that their children were juggling more than mere academic stress.
    </SubtleUnease>
    </STORYTELLER>

    <IMAGE 5>
    Late night scene. Empty plastic cups and plates scattered about a modest living room. A clock reads 4:00 a.m. John, in a casual hoodie, peers out the window. Across the street looms the Old Victorian House. High-quality visual novel style. HQ WELLSHAPED ANIME
    </IMAGE 5>
    <STORYTELLER>
    <LowTension>
    That evening, John and Jennifer hosted a friendly gathering. Music and chatter mingled with soft laughter, yet Nicole left soon after arriving, citing a sudden headache.
    </LowTension>
    <Concern>
    Long after midnight, while tidying the last remnants of the party, John noticed a dim silhouette guiding Nicole into a waiting car outside the Old Victorian House.
    </Concern>
    <Curiosity>
    The car slipped away into the shadows, leaving John uncertain whether he had just witnessed something mundane or something far more unsettling.
    </Curiosity>
    </STORYTELLER>

    <JOHN>
    <Doubt>
    "Why would Nicole vanish at this hour...? And who was that person with her...?"
    </Doubt>
    </JOHN>

    </Audiobook Narration>
<Audiobook Narration>
                    <IMAGE 6>
                    A bright lecture hall with rows of seats. John, a lean figure with short brown hair, gathers his notes at the back. Nicole, slightly hunched, sits near the front. The bandage at her neck peeks through her hair. High-quality visual novel style. HQ WELLSHAPED ANIME
                    </IMAGE 6>
                    <STORYTELLER>
                    <Contemplation>
                    Morning light pours into the lecture hall as eager students file out. Only John and Nicole linger, bound by unspoken questions and a quiet tension.
                    </Contemplation>
                    </STORYTELLER>

                    <JOHN>
                    <Nervousness>
                    "I should at least ask if she feels alright... right?"
                    </Nervousness>
                    </JOHN>

                    <NICOLE>
                    <Guarded>
                    "I just need to get through this day, no more complications... no more questions..."
                    </Guarded>
                    </NICOLE>

                    <STORYTELLER>
                    <Anticipation>
                    Their silent moment holds the promise of answers—yet neither voice dares to break it. Outside, a gentle breeze rustles the aging campus trees, as though reminding them that time waits for no one.
                    </Anticipation>
                    </STORYTELLER>
                </Audiobook Narration>